You@Hey, tell me where you last shot field artillery.
Bella@Oh, it's in the stairwell
You@The stairwell is so exciting. Where is the stairwell?
Bella@department store stairwell
You@sounds and feels wow
You@How about I unlock it too and see if we can do it over here?
You@There's no one anyway
Bella@Oh, no, let's go up. Isn't your home about to arrive?
You@Hey, I really want to try it. I haven’t unlocked it yet.
Bella@Can't it be the first time in bed?
You@Okay, let's go up first.
Bella@Walk
You@You have to accompany me from now on
Bella@OK
You@Waiting to be unlocked with you
Bella@This room is very atmospheric
You@Isn’t it suitable for what we are going to do later?
Bella@Do you mean experimentation and research spirit?
You@Of course
Bella@That
Bella@Study your bed first
Bella@Not bad
Bella@That
You@Is it time to study me instead?
Bella@Then you have to come and lie down first.
You@Let me see how powerful you are
Bella@Are you so impatient?
You@You are so beautiful. Anyone who sees you can’t help it.
Bella@Has it been like this since we were in the bar?
You@Of course, you don’t know how charming you are?
Bella@Really awesome
You@Wait a moment and you will experience something even more powerful
Bella@Then I'll do it first
Bella@Study how to take off your belt
Bella@Do you want to take it off yourself?
You@I feel like you really have a lot of experience.
Bella@Have you ever met a girl who is so considerate and helps you take off your pants?
You@Just you
Bella@real